{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Tile Roofing Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40403/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40403,"taskName":"Traditional Tile Roofing - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair a Tile Roof","xmTaskDescriptor":"Tile Roofing Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":198,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Roofers rooofing siding  conctractors","textMessagingName":"Repair Tile Roof","rolloverLongDesc":"More common in warm \u0026 arid climates, these tiles are often associated with a Latin or Mediterranean look. Nearly always a dull earthy orange color. May be hard to find experienced people to do repairs in some areas. Note separate categories for simulated tiles made from either metal or a wood-plastic composite material. This category is for when the owner is hopeful that problems can be remedied without complete replacement.","rolloverShortDesc":"Terra-cotta, often orange colored.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair a Tile Roof.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Tile Roof Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Tile Roofing \u0026 Leaks","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":65,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Traditional Tile Roof Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Traditional Tile Roofing - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Tile Roofing Project","urlName":"Traditional-Tile-Roofing-Repair","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Tile Roof Repair Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Roofers,rooofing,siding,,conctractors,roofers.com,wanted,designs,bids,,prosource,prescreened,national,local,exterior,concrete,roofs,clay,roof,Roofing,License,Traditional,build,Tile,exchange","emcCategoryOid":-12061,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":697,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376527473pwspr007F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40403/":{"taskOID":40403,"originalTaskOID":40403,"setID":697,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5146,"questionDisplayText":"Roof Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of problem do you need repaired? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Water leaking into home","answerDisplayText":"Water leaking into home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6905,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water stains on ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Water stains on ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3519,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Leaky skylight","answerDisplayText":"Leaky skylight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6870,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water is standing on the roof (after 48 hrs.)","answerDisplayText":"Water is standing on the roof (after 48 hrs.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3141,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Icicles/Ice dams at edge of roof","answerDisplayText":"Icicles/Ice dams at edge of roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1128,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Broken or rusted flashing","answerDisplayText":"Broken or rusted flashing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3667,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Loose tile(s)","answerDisplayText":"Loose tile(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6360,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Tile is cracked, broken, or missing","answerDisplayText":"Tile is cracked, broken, or missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5402,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Roof is sagging","answerDisplayText":"Roof is sagging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5144,"questionDisplayText":"Type of RoofingTile","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of roofing tile needs repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6452,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional clay tile","answerDisplayText":"Traditional clay tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3608,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lightweight concrete tile","answerDisplayText":"Lightweight concrete tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":770,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum tile","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6074,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Steel tile","answerDisplayText":"Steel tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5146,"questionDisplayText":"Roof Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of problem do you need repaired? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Water leaking into home","answerDisplayText":"Water leaking into home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6905,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water stains on ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Water stains on ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3519,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Leaky skylight","answerDisplayText":"Leaky skylight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6870,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water is standing on the roof (after 48 hrs.)","answerDisplayText":"Water is standing on the roof (after 48 hrs.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3141,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Icicles/Ice dams at edge of roof","answerDisplayText":"Icicles/Ice dams at edge of roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1128,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Broken or rusted flashing","answerDisplayText":"Broken or rusted flashing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3667,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Loose tile(s)","answerDisplayText":"Loose tile(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6360,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Tile is cracked, broken, or missing","answerDisplayText":"Tile is cracked, broken, or missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5402,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Roof is sagging","answerDisplayText":"Roof is sagging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Water leaking into home","answerDisplayText":"Water leaking into home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6905,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water stains on ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Water stains on ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3519,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Leaky skylight","answerDisplayText":"Leaky skylight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6870,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water is standing on the roof (after 48 hrs.)","answerDisplayText":"Water is standing on the roof (after 48 hrs.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3141,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Icicles/Ice dams at edge of roof","answerDisplayText":"Icicles/Ice dams at edge of roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1128,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Broken or rusted flashing","answerDisplayText":"Broken or rusted flashing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3667,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Loose tile(s)","answerDisplayText":"Loose tile(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6360,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Tile is cracked, broken, or missing","answerDisplayText":"Tile is cracked, broken, or missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5402,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Roof is sagging","answerDisplayText":"Roof is sagging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5144,"questionDisplayText":"Type of RoofingTile","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of roofing tile needs repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6452,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional clay tile","answerDisplayText":"Traditional clay tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3608,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lightweight concrete tile","answerDisplayText":"Lightweight concrete tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":770,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum tile","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6074,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Steel tile","answerDisplayText":"Steel tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6452,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Traditional clay tile","answerDisplayText":"Traditional clay tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3608,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lightweight concrete tile","answerDisplayText":"Lightweight concrete tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":770,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum tile","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6074,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Steel tile","answerDisplayText":"Steel tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}